YOSIRIS MARIÑEZ CABRERA

Junior Web Developer

@ yosiris1086@gmail.com

**** +34 664 68 07 97

Madrid

in yosiris

yosiris-m

% portfolio



ABOUT ME

Programmer by passion and Bioanalyst by choice. I come from the world of science and research, reconverted to this exciting world of programming.

Initially, I focused on languages related to frontend development, but my innate curiosity for software development prompted me to continue my studies in the training cycle that I am currently pursuing. I like teamwork, I enjoy challenges, I adapt to changes easily and I learn from them.

EXPERIENCE

Junior Frontend Developer

HeyTrade

2022 - 2023

Madrid, Remote

- I collaborated in the development of the web and mobile investment platform.
- Programmed new components in React for the web application.
- Make slight changes to the mobile application, such as creating new modal windows.
- I worked on the creation and correction of styles using the BEM methodology.
- Manage translations, import images and update color palettes from Figma.
- I updated the data in the MockServer for the simulation in the local environment.

 JavaScript
 TypeScript
 React
 SCSS
 NodeJS

Web developer

Sopra HR Software

2021 - 2022

Madrid

- Work on the maintenance and development of the web application for Human Resources management.
- Building new components in React, new screens and updated translations.
- Create test plans to evaluate website functionality.
- Designed and customized new web pages adapted for demonstrations to potential clients.

JavaScript | React | CSS | NodeJS

SKILLS

JavaScript Java(learning) TypeScript
React HTML Angular (learning)
Diseño responsive CSS SCSS
NodeJS MySQL Git Postman
Consumo de APIs REST Figma

EDUCATION

Grado superior

Desarrollo de Aplicaciones Web (DAW), Universidad Nebrija

2023 - Present

Bootcamps

Desarrollo Web, Adalab Digital

₩ 2021

Introducción al Desarrollo Web, Bejob, Universidad de Alcalá

2021

Bachelor's Degree

Degree in Bioanalysis, Universidad Central del Este, Dom. Rep.

₩ 2009

CERTIFICATIONS

Análisis y programación en Java, Nascor-Formación

₩ 2023

Generation K, Kairós DS

2023